Yeah,
there is someone I like.
I…
love Reo Amano.
Then that makes us rivals.
This feels so nostalgic.
Many girls used to declare war to me over Reo.
I didn't lose back in middle school,
however...
Mai, was it?
His current girlfriend?
It seems romance never goes well.
[Ai-Chan's Secret | Episode 9]
Things aren't over within Yuka's heart.
She's always wholeheartedly loved Reo.
When I saw Yuka like that,
I felt like I needed to be honest, even if it spilled my secret.
So you told her you love Reo, and now it's like you two are comrades.
Yeah, something like that.
And now you're feeling unsure?
Were you also frustrated that you couldn't say, “I’m Mai”?
Yeah. I thought I was being unfair.
Jeez, you're so honest when you're in love!
You don't need to be considerate of his ex.
You're Reo's current girlfriend.
But I don't think Reo broke up because he wanted to either.
An ex-girlfriend
knows a version of our partner, unknown to us.
We become uneasy, because that's unchangeable.
Yeah.
Even so, Reo says it's over.
All we can do is believe him.
That's what I've decided to do.
Which means… you've forgiven Ritsuki?
Yes.
I'm a fool, aren't I?
Despite it all, I love him.
That's why
I'll believe in Ritsuki.
I see.
[Just finished my shift. What are you up to?]
He's probably
at his part-time job... right?
You're the one who let go,
Yuka.
[Kafuu High School]
Wow, seriously?
Is Reo's ex that much of a beauty?
Yeah, she won the pageant at her middle school, and her personality's great.
That's amazing!
Then, Reo confessed to her.
- For real?!
- For real.
Of course they suit one another.
It was a real spectacle.
Tell me the details.
Sure.
Why not chase them and ask?
I don't want to know.
That ex was the exact opposite of you.
Are you jealous?
I'm not.
His ex-girlfriend may be more stubborn than anticipated.
Takumi,
are you one to quickly forget about a girl you liked?
You're gonna ask me?
Sorry.
Let yourself be vulnerable, and I'll kiss you.
You idiot. What the hell.
Are you worried about Reo?
Not really.
Don't worry. You have
your own, unique charms.
That's none of your business.
Thanks.
- I want to buy new sneakers.
- Same here.
- Really?
- Yeah, my current ones don't support my ankles.
- Makes sense.
- What're you guys talking about?
- Buying new basketball shoes.
- For Reo?
[Do you have time after practice today?]
[Sorry, I have plans today]
[I'll make time for you]
Did Reo leave?
Yes, he seemed to be in a hurry.
- Yeah.
- Maybe he has a date?
Possibly.
Thanks.
Thank you!
Thank you for your patronage!
Why?
Ken told me.
That bastard.
How long have you been with Reo?
How long...?
How long have you two been dating?
About three months.
Thank goodness.
See you again.
Well...
Don't you have business with Reo?
I'll try another day. It's something I can't discuss around you.
Give up on him.
It's not that easy.
Good work.
Aiko?
Sorry. To tell you the truth,
Hiroko, Ikumi and I tailed you the other day.
For real?
I'm sure you're put off by that.
Not at all.
I'm happy.
You could've told me about your part-time job.
Isn't there something else you want to say?
I'll listen to every last thing
you want to tell me.
That's why you came, right?
You won't hate me?
Of course I won't.
I don't know what to do.
I wonder what you're doing after practice.
I feel down, just because you haven't read my texts.
I anxiously think about how you may be seeing Yuka.
I don't want to think about it, and I want to believe you.
But I keep thinking about how you might choose Yuka after all.
It's the first time I've loved someone this much.
Reo,
you're the first person I've ever dated.
I don't know what to do.
And today, I—
Wow,
I totally lost my cool.
That wasn't what I wanted to say.
I'm really
sorry.
Aiko...
[I'll be returning to Kagoshima the day after tomorrow]
[Can we meet, one last time?]
That was so uncool.
So unlike me.
Let's eat and forget all about it.
- What does it mean to be "like oneself"?
- Huh?
So, what does it mean to be, "Aiko"?
"More manly then men",
and, "the ace of our girls basketball team"?
It's unlike me to overthink things.
Yet, I ambushed him with so much.
Now it's awkward, and I'm embarrassed.
What's wrong with being uncool?
Romance isn't all about showing your good side.
You discovered new sides to yourself, and told him how you felt, despite the mess.
You're not uncool at all.
Reo...
Sorry I made you anxious.
I'm going to end it, for good.
Will you come with me tonight?
A confrontation with his ex-girlfriend?
Seems like it.
Where? I'll go too.
Ikumi.
I'm worried if it's just Mai.
That other girl is aggressively aiming for Reo.
Look at a mirror before saying that.
Mai is too kind for her own good.
That's what makes her charming.
I thought you were loyal to Ai?
The order is up.
- Okay.
Actually, I'll—
Stay seated.
Thank you for waiting. Here is your coffee.
Please enjoy.
Yuka...
I have no intention of meeting behind her back.
If you're okay with that,
I'll listen to whatever you have to say.
That's all right.
After all, I don't want to hold any more regrets.
I wanted to explain what happened back then.
My stomach… I'm going to the restroom!
Her intentions are plain as day.
You can't hate her, can you?
I see.
I'm no longer a part of you.
Even so...
you still remain within me.
To be honest,
I know why you left without a word.
I heard your parents divorced,
and you went with your mother.
There was the option to have a long distance relationship,
but you had us break up, cause I was weak, right?
- No.
- "Long distance is impossible,
and it'd be unbearable..."
That's what I would've said back then.
No, that's not it.
I thought distance would cause misunderstandings.
If we were to hurt one another and break up, then I'd rather...
I didn't want to hate you, Reo.
Even so,
I seriously loved you.
I wanted to face those issues, and find answers, together.
You're right.
Now, I agree with you.
Yuka, you'll never disappear
from within me.
You're the first person I seriously loved.
However, neither time
nor feelings
can return to what they use to be.
She made me realize something.
You're really good!
Say… Let’s join the basketball club together!
I'm Aiko Kasumi.
She made me realize
I'd try falling in love again.
♫ What awaits in this battle of love? ♫
♫ It seems it won't end in a draw ♫
♫ You hated loosing, ♫
How shameful of me.
♫ So I won't let you go easy on me ♫
Reo, you've moved on a long time ago.
♫ I don't wish for anyone to know my secret ♫
♫ I want to steal you away ♫
♫ The secret that belongs to only us. ♫
Yuka!
I'm sorry.
I need to be honest with you.
I'm... actually—
Wait.
Aiko?
As I thought.
So, you realized.
On our second… no, third meeting?
When we saw each other at Reo's part-time job,
I thought you two sounded similar.
So you're his girlfriend, Aiko.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't apologize.
The fact that I’m Reo’s first girlfriend,
will now be something you remember.
That makes us even.
♫ Rather than touching, we can melt
into one another's embrace ♫
♫ I'll let you get near just to return you like a wave ♫
This is the end.
♫ Lips to exchange ♫
Good bye.
Meddlesome, reckless, selfish.
How else should I describe you?
Reo...
are you mad?
No.
Let's go home.
You're not curious to hear what we talked about?
The memories you two share...
should stay between you two.
That's why
I don't need to know.
When I spoke with Yuka,
there was something I remembered.
I want
to break up with "Mai".
Instead,
I want to date "Aiko".
I didn't fall for you as "Mai".
The one I love,
is none other then "Aiko Kasumi".
[Kasumi]
Next Sunday,
I want you to come as Aiko. For real this time.
Game face, on.
- I'm sleepy.
- Today's herbal tea will be chamomile.
Morning.
Perfect temperature,
perfect smell.
- Whoa!
- What's the matter?
Is there a wedding today?
- No, today's "that".
- "That"?
Oh yeah, yeah.
What's "that"?
Why are you so far apart?
I'm not on my A game.
Look in front of you.
Amazing!
This fish looks tasty! Is it a sardine?
Do you only think about eating? It's definitely not a sardine.
- Or maybe it is?
- Look over there.
- A total hottie.
- Is that his girlfriend?
♫ Just wanna, wanna, wanna, wanna go and take it ♫
♫ You take my heart too ♫
♫ Just wanna, wanna, wanna, wanna  ♫
♫ Go and take it ♫
I wonder if it's all right that I'm "Aiko".
I like you, because you're "Aiko".
Aiko, happy birthday.
Did you forget your own birthday?
Yeah.
Let me see that.
We're like a couple.
We are a couple.
I've determined
not to let you go, no matter what.
I plan to be with you, forever.
That's what I thought about,
when buying these pair rings.
Say something.
Thanks!
I love you so much!
[Kafuu High School]
Whoa, is that...
Yeah, it is.
A pair with Mai, huh?
- What the heck?
- I'm shocked.
- It's definitely her.
- Aiko...
Aiko, what's the meaning of this?
♫ I make you acting like a kid with just a sweet kiss ♫
Were you on a date with Reo?
Reo and Ai were on a date?
♫ Rather than touching, we can melt
into one another's embrace ♫
[Next time]
Merry Christmas!
[Ai-Chan's Secret, Finale]
I want to tell everyone that you're mine, Aiko.
[The secret that they've protected, together]
I don't deserve to be Reo's girlfriend.
[Everyone's feelings accelerate]
- This is my final gamble.
- Kiss me.
By overcoming many hurdles, Ai has changed.
To tell you the truth, I'm Aiko Kasumi.
[It's Christmas night. How will this secret love conclude?]